<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN"
    "http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">

<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
  <meta name="generator" content=
  "HTML Tidy for Windows (vers 14 February 2006), see www.w3.org" />
  <meta content="text/html; charset=us-ascii" http-equiv=
  "content-type" />
  <title>Jobs Dashboard Help</title>
  <body>
    <LINK REL="StyleSheet" HREF="../../plugins/JobsDashboard/pluginhelp.css" TYPE="text/css" MEDIA="screen"/>
    	<div class="help">
        <p>
    	<a href="JobsDashboardMain_run">Jobs Dashboard</a>
  		</p>
		<p><a href="configureDashboard_run">Configure Dashboard</a></p>
        <h1 class="help" id="jobsdashboard">Jobs Dashboard</h1>
        <p class="help">Plugin Version 2.0.0</p>
        <hr style="margin-left: -10px; margin-top: 10px; border: 1px solid #112D80; background-color:#112D80;"
        noshade="noshade" />
      
        <p class="help">
        The Jobs Dashboard provides a front-end user interface for monitoring jobs.  
        </p>
        
       
    <ul>
	<li>Conveniently view your running jobs, job progress, job status, and historical job outcomes in a graphical format.</li>
	<li>Easily access "Dashboard Configuration" to configure and add a Project's Procedures to the Jobs Dashboard.</li>
	<li>Customizable job history count and refresh rate.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<p class="help">
        You simply need to add your project's procedures to the Jobs Dashboard to get started. Click the "Configure Dashboard" link at the top of this page and add your project's procedures to the Jobs Dashboard to get started.
	</p>
	
       <h1 class="help" id="gettingstarted">Getting started</h1>
       <hr style="margin-left: -10px; margin-top: 10px; border: 1px solid #112D80; background-color:#112D80;"
        noshade="noshade" />
        
        <p class="help">
        <b>Prerequisite:</b> If you are new to Commander or new to this Commander feature, the dashboard is blank, similar to the following screen example. You need to add the procedures whos jobs you want to monitor.
        </p>
        
        <img src="../../plugins/JobsDashboard/images/emptyDashboard.png" alt="" />
               
        <h2 class="help">Dashboard Configuration</h2>
       
       <ul> 
	<li>Click the <b>Configure Dashboard</b> link at the top of this page or at the top right of the Jobs Dashboard. You will be taken to a page similar to the screen example below.</li>	
	        
	        <img src="../../plugins/JobsDashboard/images/configureDashboard.png" alt="" />
	        
	<li>Choose a Dashboard Title, Project Column Header and Procedure Column Header.</li>	
	<li>Choose a numeric value for History which is the number of job results that are shown for each procedure.</li> 
	<li>Choose a numeric value for Refresh Rate which is the rate at which the information will be updated.</li> 
	<li>In the <b>Select Projects and procedures to monitor</b> section, Click the + to expand the list of project.</li>
	<li>For each project, click the + to view the project's procedures and check the boxes for the procedures you want to monitor.</li> 
	<li>Click the Save button.</li>
		</ul>
	<h1 class="help">Jobs Dashboard</h1>
        <hr style="margin-left: -10px; margin-top: 10px; border: 1px solid #112D80; background-color:#112D80;"
        noshade="noshade" />
        
        <h2 class="help">Understanding dashboard navigation and visual representations</h2>
        
        <p class="help">
        The Job Dashboard centralizes all of your build information in a summerized visual interface. In addition to the information available visually, the Dashboard contains the links for navigation to job details pages.
        </p>
        
        <p class="help">
        The next screen example shows how your dashboard will look as you populate it with job configurations:
        </p>
        
        <img src="../../plugins/JobsDashboard/images/dashboardWithJobs.png" alt="" />
        
        <h4 class="help">Column descriptions</h4>
        
        <table class="grid">
        <col width="150" />
  	<col width="750" />
	   <thead>
	      <tr class="tablehead">
	        <th>Column heading</th>
	        <th>Description</th>
	      </tr>
	   </thead>
	
	   <tbody>
		<tr>
		<td style="vertical-align:top">Projects</td>
		<td>Your project names appear in bold font in this column. Expanding the project displays a list of all procedures chosen for monitoring for the project.<br/><br/></td>
		</tr>
	
		<tr>
		<td style="vertical-align:top">Procedures</td>
		<td>The Procedure names appear in this column.</td>
		</tr>

		<tr>
		<td style="vertical-align:top">Success Ratio</td>
		<td>A visual representation tracking the percentage of your successful jobs. A higher percentage indicates more builds are running successfully. <b>The ratio is based on the number of jobs displayed on the dashboard.</b> If the project is collapsed, this percentage reflects the combined success rate for all procedures in the project.</td>
		</tr>
			
		<tr>
		<td style="vertical-align:top">Jobs (Old -> New)</td>
		<td>Each time a new job completes, you will see a color-coded tile indicating the status of the job (success, warning, or failure). Hover your mouse over a tile to see job information or to go to the Job Details page for that job. The most recent job appears on the right-side of this column. "Gray" or uncolored boxes on the left-side of the column are place-holders for jobs that have not run yet. If no jobs have run for that procedure, it will be indicated with a "no jobs found" label</td>
		</tr>
	
		<tr>
		<td style="vertical-align:top">Last Run Details</td>
		<td>This column provides additional information on the last run job. Indicating who it was run by and the name of the job.</td>
		</tr>
	
		<tr>
		<td style="vertical-align:top">Description</td>
		<td>This column provides the description for the procedure</td>
		</tr>
	   </tbody>
	</table>
        
                

    </div>      
  </body>
  </head>
</html>
