<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN"
    "http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">

<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
  <meta name="generator" content=
  "HTML Tidy for Windows (vers 14 February 2006), see www.w3.org" />
  <meta content="text/html; charset=us-ascii" http-equiv=
  "content-type" />
  <title>Workflows Dashboard Help</title>
  <body>
    <LINK REL="StyleSheet" HREF="../../plugins/WorkflowDashboard/pluginhelp.css" TYPE="text/css" MEDIA="screen"/>
    	<div class="help">
        <p>
    	<a href="workflowDashboardMain_run">Workflows Dashboard</a>
  		</p>
		<p><a href="configureDashboard_run">Configure Dashboard</a></p>
        <h1 class="help" id="Workflowdashboard">Workflows Dashboard</h1>
        <p class="help">Plugin Version</p>
        <hr style="margin-left: -10px; margin-top: 10px; border: 1px solid #112D80; background-color:#112D80;"
        noshade="noshade" />
      
        <p class="help">
        The Workflows Dashboard provides a front-end user interface for monitoring workflows.  
        </p>
        
       
    <ul>
	<li>Conveniently view your running workflows, workflow progress, workflow status, and historical workflow outcomes in a graphical format.</li>
	<li>Easily access the Dashboard Configuration to configure and add a Project's Workflows to the Dashboard.</li>
	<li>Customizable History Count, Success Threshold, Errors Threshold,  and Refresh Rate.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<p class="help">
        You simply need to add your project's workflows to the Dashboard to get started. Click the "Configure Dashboard" link at the top of this page and add your project's workflows to the Dashboard to get started.
	</p>
	
       <h1 class="help" id="gettingstarted">Getting started</h1>
       <hr style="margin-left: -10px; margin-top: 10px; border: 1px solid #112D80; background-color:#112D80;"
        noshade="noshade" />
        
        <p class="help">
        <b>Prerequisite:</b> If you are new to Commander or new to this Commander feature, the Workflows Dashboard is blank, similar to the following screen example. You need to add the workflows you want to monitor.
        </p>
        
        <img src="../../plugins/WorkflowDashboard/images/emptyDashboard.png" alt="" />
               
        <h2 class="help">Dashboard Configuration</h2>
       
       <ul> 
	<li>Click the <b>Configure Dashboard</b> link at the top of this page or at the top right of the Dashboard. You will be taken to a page similar to the screen example below.</li>	
	        
	        <img src="../../plugins/WorkflowDashboard/images/configureDashboard.png" alt="" />
	        
	<li>Choose a Dashboard Title, Project Column Header and workflow Column Header.</li>	
	<li>Choose a numeric value for History which is the number of job results that are shown for each workflow.</li> 
	<li>Choose a numeric value for History which is the number of job results that are shown for each workflow.</li> 
	<li>Choose a numeric value for Success Threshold and for the Error Threshold.</li> 
	<li>In the <b>Select Projects and Workflows to monitor</b> section, Click the + to expand the list of project.</li>
	<li>For each project, click the + to view the project's workflows and check the boxes for the workflows you want to monitor.</li> 
	<li>Click the Save button.</li>
		</ul>
	<h1 class="help">Workflows Dashboard</h1>
        <hr style="margin-left: -10px; margin-top: 10px; border: 1px solid #112D80; background-color:#112D80;"
        noshade="noshade" />
        
        <h2 class="help">Understanding dashboard navigation and visual representations</h2>
        
        <p class="help">
        The Workflows Dashboard centralizes all of your build information in a summerized visual interface. In addition to the information available visually, the Dashboard contains the links for navigation to job details pages.
        </p>
        
        <p class="help">
        The next screen example shows how your dashboard will look as you populate it with job configurations:
        </p>
        
        <img src="../../plugins/WorkflowDashboard/images/dashboardWithJobs.png" alt="" />
        
        <h4 class="help">Column descriptions</h4>
        
        <table class="grid">
        <col width="150" />
  	<col width="750" />
	   <thead>
	      <tr class="tablehead">
	        <th>Column heading</th>
	        <th>Description</th>
	      </tr>
	   </thead>
	
	   <tbody>
		<tr>
		<td style="vertical-align:top">Projects</td>
		<td>Your project names appear in bold font in this column. Expanding the project displays a list of all workflows chosen for monitoring for the project.<br/><br/></td>
		</tr>
	
		<tr>
		<td style="vertical-align:top">workflow</td>
		<td>The workflow names appear in this column.</td>
		</tr>
			
		<tr>
		<td style="vertical-align:top">workflows (Old -> New)</td>
		<td>Each time a new workflow completes, you will see a color-coded tile indicating the status of the workflow (success, warning, manual step or failure). Hover your mouse over a tile to see job information and the content of the workflow property ec_workflow_description if it exists; or to go to the Job Details page for that job. The most recent job appears on the right-side of this column. "Gray" or uncolored boxes on the left-side of the column are place-holders for workflows that have not run yet. If no workflows have run, it will be indicated with a "no workflows found" label</td>
		</tr>
	
		<tr>
		<td style="vertical-align:top">Last Run Details</td>
		<td>This column provides additional information on the last run job. Indicating who it was started by, the current state and the name of the job.</td>
		</tr>
	
		<tr>
		<td style="vertical-align:top">Risk</td>
		<td>This column provides a color coded image representing the risk for the workflow</td>
		</tr>
				
		<tr>
		<td style="vertical-align:top">Avg Cycle Time</td>
		<td>This column provides Average Cycle Time for the workflow</td>
		</tr>
	   </tbody>
	</table>
        
                

    </div>      
  </body>
  </head>
</html>
